[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Black Iberian Pig?", "correct_answer": "It is indigenous to the Mediterranean.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is a rodent.", "All of these", "It is not actually black."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who turned down the the role of Shug Avery in the movie The Color Purple?", "correct_answer": "Tina Turner", "incorrect_answers": ["Oprah Winfrey", "Aretha Franklin", "Gladys Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zong Zi is a traditional food for this country. It is a rice dumpling wrapped in bamboo or reed leaves.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Thailand", "Japan", "Singapore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Goats milk is the most consumed milk in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leather can bring out the best in some females.  Which feline fatale said  Youre the second man who killed me this week but Ive got seven lives left.?", "correct_answer": "Catwoman", "incorrect_answers": ["Storm", "Daredevil", "Miss Kitty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Socrates, the ideal state had this type of governmental control.", "correct_answer": "Military communism", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Absolute monarchy", "Democracy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Color therapy assumes that each color influences differently our moods, levels of energy and even mental state and abilities. What is the color red usually associated with?", "correct_answer": "Passion and strength", "incorrect_answers": ["Higher mental capability", "Calmness and purity", "Optimism and joy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name do Ellie and Manny give to their first-born child in the 2009 animated movie Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "Peaches", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Ellie", "Sid", "Scrattie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This heavy metal has the symbol Pb. It is a poisonous neurotoxin that can cause brain and blood disorders.", "correct_answer": "Lead", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Chloride", "Chromium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fred Gage and Peter Ericksson discovered and announced that adult human brain produces new brain cells. In what year did they make their discovery?", "correct_answer": "1998", "incorrect_answers": ["1992", "1997", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do the McCallister family reside in the great 90s movie Home Alone?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Detroit", "Philadelphia", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the legend, which of these is a part of the Three Fortunate Concealments that protect Britain from any danger coming from the sea?", "correct_answer": "The head of Bran the Blessed", "incorrect_answers": ["Stone of Destiny", "The Dragons", "The bones of Gwerthefyr the Blessed"]}]